Golden lines sketch a city.
Smoke billows from etched smokestacks.
The glowing city shrinks away.
The glowing figure stands tall.
A dark, angular figure appears, raising a hand among the faithful.
The demon reaches out with jagged claws. The faithful scatter in terror.
A faithful warrior battles the heretic.
The warrior strikes him down.
The glowing murals decorate the walls of a dark, hexagonal chamber.
A Vodyani leader stands tall.
Clad in a bulky black suit with a glowing orange faceplate, the figure holds a long staff.
The balcony sits within the windowed bridge of a colossal starship.
Outside in the void, a massive fleet of jagged vessels flanks the great Ark.
Glowing orange thrusters propel the armada forward into the starry expanse.
Everything fades to black.